Hello hi guys welcome to my ji my name
is denge isko math today I am going to talk to the people
about the arrangement yes
about health insurance so see if you are
running this business then what has happened now is that
you have called your employees to many offices so guys it becomes
your duty to
keep your employees in good health so today I am going to
tell you how you
can get the cheapest of the cheapest insurance for your employees so that they have
supported you till now, have supported
us, have supported your company, have
supported your business so it is your duty to
protect them as well they are so
secure is it a shot that the
company is also listening to us, providing us
protection, is purchasing such insurance for us so guys
today
I am going to tell you some more mid-day plans
which are
available to you online at very cheap rates so let's start so let's start with that
actress Kajol insurance  There is a difference between these plans and the
other normal traction health
insurance plans.
So, see what happened in 2019, the
government of
India had issued an advisory,
which is the main body of all the companies. IRDA, which basically
controls all the insurance
companies, had given guidelines that
you should get Vitamin E relief. Regarding
health insurance Maghrib and Isha Zip,
many companies have come up with a one-
time offer, you can say it is
Vinyasa Health Insurance Plan, in which
you can get insurance against any disease by paying a very small premium for one year.
What is inside this normal policy, in that
you get equal
principle admits lapses. In this, you are
covered for some time and if you get any disease,
it is also covered, but this
actress Kate Winslet, who is buying from online plan
or offline job line, is getting insurance from electricity for
corona, if your report
comes positive then only you will be able to
get this policy, so I  Regarding the plans, I
would like to tell you that digital
plans are available
on many platforms like Paytm, Flipkart, Paytm,
Phone, these plans are available on all these
but the thing to be noted is that these
plans have made some shortcomings that
these people have entered into with third party
providers, which
reduces the insurance like Reliance, it has become a
long thread like IIT, so on
enrolment with all these, you have to pay the interest on that, so first of all let me
talk about Paytm, if
you talk about ATM then it is the
best plan available here, here
for reminder, if you pay Rs 466
then you get a shot of Rs 50 thousand, you
get a medical shop, in which
if you have a child from 3 months onwards, here in 37,
if you have an insurance from
anywhere in the family, you
can get the insurance of that, after 15 days of
taking Pretty Priya's Bal Kavita insurance,
this policy
gets implemented for 15 days  You will have to wait
and after that talk about the
Congress expenses, so
pre and post hospitalization,
whatever treatment will be done before the hospitalization, whatever
tests will be done or whatever
expenses will be incurred, all of that is covered, after that all the
expenses that are incurred after going to the hospital,
so here you get only 466 to
50,000 from the best medical insurance,
why talk about the other friend, all the other conditions are there but
you have to pay 515 for this and
it is noted ₹1000, in the third plan, ₹
13 and ₹2 and this amount keeps increasing to
2 lakh rupees and the fourth plan is of 1948 in
which you get medical insurance of full 3 lakh rupees, in a way,
now I will talk about the
second company which is Flipkart,
Flipkart has typed here with DG Insurance,
Prince, let me tell you
that action is being taken against Reliance General Insurance Company through Paytm Bhejo Pradhan Available Act
Which is
considered to be a very well known company,
why talk about Flipkart and with tyre DJ
insurance, then look at size
insurance and that is why the new brand has come in
insurance but online
it is quite popular, if you talk about government plans
then it comes to you for ₹499, in which you will
definitely get
one lakh in ₹525 and in ₹3 lakh in ₹563, if you
talk about the insurance that they do on the phone, I have typed with Bajaj Allianz
and right now they have only one
plan which starts from ₹10 in
which you get only ₹50,000,
after that they have launched it
in India, so they have tied up with ICC Lombard
and they provide you tyre kit
in ₹598, there is a line thief in it, after that, there is
definitely a fixed singer Hansraj Hans
and service provider company, it is a little
difficult and a very popular
brand, this Star Health
Insurance is quite important  Through a well-known health
insurance company, after this, the company
launched a plan regarding the quality, whose starting price is
considered to be ₹1000 in 353 and ₹420 in 796,
which leaves asthma. If there is any
drawback in this, there are many such drawbacks, for
which you can contact directly
and basically you can definitely try your plan. If it is
called Kavach policy, then you will find it
in the description here, you will find an
article here, you can see that a comparison has been
given for all the leading companies, how much is the
premium of each one, and if you go for bun hair, then how much will it be for
two passengers, so in this
way, if you make a chart here,
it will help a lot. Now let me talk about
how you should decide which
company's plan to buy. So guys, my message to all of you is
that third party means that you should
not go by the brand name, Paytm,
Flipkart, do not go by these, now you can
see for yourself, but with drawbacks.  If you have filed a claim
and how much is their claim settlement in Odisha, then
you should go to their website and check
how is the country in your home area
and also find out when the process of the plan
agreement is done, many things are processed
like personal gain experience, there is a
process for many things that you simply submit an online
request,
upload the documents online and all the things which will be done
online for your claim, for the
process of your claim you have to
fill a physical form, then there is the
address, you have to clear it there so that
your nails and they want to
do it with everyone, so guys
you should know that the claim
process is so simple,
how much the
person, keeping all the things in mind,
you can easily get insurance for your employer, your family
member or anyone, so guys please
like this video, if you have a job
then like in the comment section, you will definitely win the matching,
thank you my son